[Music]
hello guys this is your coach dan
your financial advisor and before we
start
let me just say thank you again to
everyone who subscribed to my channel i
really really do appreciate it
if you are new here and you haven't
subscribed yet please click
on the subscribe button and also the
notification bell so you'll be notified
whenever i post
videos on financial planning and
managing your personal finances
today
so if you're ready let's begin first
step is to go to bdo's website
at wwe
on the upper right hand corner of the
website click on bdo
online banking for you to be able to log
into your bdo
online account
[Music]
after logging into your account click on
enrollment
company biller and then enroll
for the company or biller's name look
for sun life of canada philippines inc
input your policy number for the
subscriber number
and type in the name of the owner of the
sun life policy you are enrolling
make sure that online banking is checked
under channel for enrollment
once you're done click submit and
confirm the enrollment
by clicking ok
congratulations you've just enrolled
your sun life policy and you're now
ready to make your first payment
by a bdo online
to make a payment click pay bills and
reload
bills payment and then pay bills
schedule on a regular basis in payments
and there you have it now you can make
your payments
via bdo online or the bdo mobile app
if you learned something new today click
the like button
leave a comment and make sure to
[Music]
subscribe